...you might make this a viable business.
(Penny:)And you know about that stuff?
(Sheldon:)Penny.
(Sheldon:)I'm a physicist.
(Sheldon:)I have a working knowledge of the entire
universe and everything it contains.
(Penny:)Who's Radiohead?
(Sheldon:)I have a working knowledge
of the important things in the universe.
(Sheldon:)- Good luck.
- Sheldon, hold on.
(Penny:)Could you maybe show me
how to make more money with this?
(Sheldon:)Of course I could.
(Penny:)Sheldon, wait.
(Penny:)Will you?
(Sheldon:)Just to be clear here.
(Sheldon:)You're asking for my assistance.
(Penny:)Yes.
(Sheldon:)And you understand that will involve me
telling you what to do?
(Penny:)I understand.
(Sheldon:)And you're not allowed to be sarcastic
or snide to me while I'm doing so.
(Penny:)Okay.
(Sheldon:)Good.
(Sheldon:)Let's begin with the premise that everything
you've done up to this point is wrong.
- Oh, imagine that.
- Sarcasm. Goodbye.
No, I'm sorry. Wait. Please, come back.